(Bernadette:)What will pay for itself?
(Howard:)Doesn't matter.
What are you mad about?
(Bernadette:)I'm mad at you
for blabbing to me
(Bernadette:)what Leonard did
on the North Sea,
(Bernadette:)and I'm mad that
I've had to hide this
(Bernadette:)from Penny for two years.
(Howard:)And you have every right to
be mad about those things.
(Howard:)So, why don't you let me
(Howard:)handle the credit card
bill this month, huh?
(Howard:)I mean, don't
even look at it.
(Bernadette:)I mean, if Penny finds out
I've known all this time
(Bernadette:)and haven't told her,
(Bernadette:)she's gonna think
I'm a terrible friend.
(Bernadette:)I wish you never told me.
(Howard:)And I wish Leonard
never told me.
(Howard:)He's the bad guy here.
(Bernadette:)I guess that's true.
(Howard:)And you let
Penny marry him.
(scoffs)
(Howard:)Compared to that,
who cares if I bought
(Howard:)a George Clooney limited
edition manscaping kit?
(Leonard(on phone):)Hi. I'm calling about your
marriage counseling services